adtraction.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Adtraction Affiliate Network

## Introduction

Data privacy and safe processing of personal data is a priority for Adtraction. Those who provide Adtraction with personal data must be able to trust that the personal data is processed in accordance with applicable personal data legislation, for example the EU General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679) ("GDPR"), which enter into force on 25 May 2018.

Adtraction have taken great measures to be GDPR compliant and this Privacy Policy has been created in order for you to better understand how information is processed by Adtraction. This Privacy Policy is not exhaustive, but contains some fundamental privacy principles applied by Adtraction to safeguard the integrity of individuals.

Adtraction may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to keep it compliant with applicable laws such as the GDPR.

Adtraction and in some cases its subsidiaries are responsible for personal data provided to Adtraction.

## Adtraction's processing of personal data

### Definitions

Personal data comprises all types of information that directly or indirectly can be linked to an individual, including name, address or telephone number.

### Personal data that Adtraction processes

Adtraction collects and processes several types of personal data, all depending on the situation. Examples of such personal data are: names, addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, IP-addresses, personal identity numbers, bank account numbers or other information that you provide within the framework of Adtraction's service.

### Personal data which Adtraction process when you visit Adtraction's website

If you are only using the website for information and do not register or transmit information to us in any other way, we only collect the personal data which your browser transmits to our server. If you wish to view our website, we collect the following data that are technically necessary for us to display our website to you and guarantee its stability and security (the legal basis is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 lit. f GDPR):

  * IP address
  * Date and time of the enquiry
  * Time zone difference from Greenwich Mean Time (GMT)
  * Content of the request (specific page)
  * Access status / HTTP status code
  * Quantity of data transferred in each case
  * The website from which the request comes
  * Browser
  * Operating system and its interface
  * Language and version of the browser software.

### Purpose of processing personal data

Personal data is used to provide access to Adtraction's services, to pay Affiliates, for administration, internal analysis and to fulfill other commitments. Your personal data may also be processed for additional purposes according to applicable law or agreements.

### Transfer of personal data and disclosure of personal data

Personal data can be handled by Adtraction's subsidiaries and subcontractors/processors if this is necessary to achieve the purpose for which the personal data has been collected.

Adtraction does not rent or sell personal information to third parties and does not divulge personal information without written consent of the interested party, except to comply with legal inquiries, when it is required by law or otherwise when it is necessary to detect and prevent criminal activity.

### Consent and rights

Where it is required by law or where Adtraction otherwise deems it appropriate, Adtraction will seek consent from you before Adtraction processes your personal data.

You have the right to recall consent to process personal data that you have provided to Adtraction. The recall must be in writing. You also have the right to request that personal data concerning you is erased, rectified or restricted.

You have the right to obtain information of the personal data concerning you which is being processed by Adtraction. You also have the right to access such personal data in a digital format and/or to lodge a complaint of Adtraction's processing of personal data to the Swedish Data Protection Authority.

Adtraction strives to ensure that necessary measures are taken to delete or de-identify personal information that is incorrect or no longer needed by Adtraction for the purposes for which the personal data was collected.

### Security

Adtraction has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect personal data against unauthorized access, destruction and change as well as ensuring that only personal data which is necessary for each specific processing purpose is processed.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file stored in your browser. The cookie contains no personal information and no connection is made between such information and a visitor's identity.

Adtraction's usage of cookies is handled within the framework of the GDPR and other applicable legislation.

If you do not want to receive cookies, you can change your settings in your browser. However, this can cause websites to stop working properly. How to disable cookies depends on which browser you use. Read the "Help" or equivalent menu in your browser for further instructions.

### Web analysis with Google Analytics

Adtraction's website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (Google). Google Analytics uses cookies, i.e. text files stored on your computer to enable analysis of website usage by you. Information generated by the cookie about your use of Adtraction's website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the United States and stored there. In case of activated IP anonymization on Adtraction's website, however, your IP address is previously truncated by Google within member states of the European Union or in other states which are party to the agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is a full IP address transmitted to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. On behalf of Adtraction, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports about website activities, and provide the website's operator with further services related to website and Internet usage. The IP address sent from your browser as part of Google Analytics is not merged with other data by Google. You can prevent storage of cookies by appropriately setting your browser software; in this case, however, please note that you might not be able to fully use all functions offered by Adtraction's website. In addition, you can prevent data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) from being collected and processed by Google, by downloading and installing a browser plug-in.

Adtraction's website uses Google Analytics with the extension "anonymizeIP()", IP addresses being truncated before further processing in order to rule out direct associations to persons. The legal basis for the use of Google Analytics is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 lit. f GDPR.

### Social plug-ins from Facebook

We use social plug-ins from facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plug-ins can be recognized by way of the Facebook logo or the supplement "Facebook Social Plug-in". For example, if you click on the "Like" button or leave a comment, the relevant information is transmitted directly from your browser to Facebook and stored there. Furthermore, Facebook makes your likes public for your Facebook friends. If you are logged into Facebook, it can assign the invocation of our page directly to your Facebook account. Even if you are not logged in or do not have a Facebook account, your browser sends information (e.g. which web pages you have called up, your IP address) which is then stored by Facebook. For details about handling of your personal data by Facebook and your related rights, please refer to the data privacy policy of Facebook. If you do not want Facebook to map data collected about you via Adtraction's web sites to your Facebook account, you must log out of Facebook before you visit Adtraction's web pages. The legal basis for the use of plug-ins is Article 6 (1) sentence 1 lit. f GDPR.

### Contact information

If you have any questions about Adtraction's handling of personal data, please contact Adtraction at info@adtraction.com or +46 8-35 92 00.
